Stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make a stand!
The paint within brings
out a map of your own.
To the left and the right,
all we saw stormy nights.
All the rough winds and
waves coming day after day?
And the values we had were about to
collapse Oh, just where do we go next?
And as we look down to the compass in
hand Is it showing us the right direction?
All we know is nobody
here knows it for certain.
So close your eyes and breathe in deeply.
And listen to your soul.
You'll see a path in front of you.
And you'll know just where you need to go.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make us stand.
Don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
I'll do it my own way,
that's what's best for me.
And you do it your way,
that's how it's got to be.
We're moving forward, now I'm ready.
But at times it's okay
to get help on the way.
For the future ahead, burning bright.
For what's ahead you see?
Is beyond your wildest dreams.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand,
cut through the wind and make A stand,
don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
We'll do it our way,
the best that we know.
With tears and doubts and tone,
we'll go where we all want to go.
The page within brings colors of our own.
I'll finish you before you
even have a chance to fight.
I don't think so.
Kawamatsu, splendid work.
Let's join the Straw Hats
and take out the big guys.
Don't even think about it, you two.
It isn't our place to help them.
Not in this battle.
Can't you see that?
I don't understand, boss.
They're fighting the lead performers.
We must keep both our enemies and
our allies away from the battle
Look at their faces.
They're saying don't get in our way
On top of the red line
Only thing up there is Marie Joie.
There's no gods.
It's not like you to be
superstitious. What gives?
Are you drunk or something, Pops?
Maybe so.
There's nothing worth
seeing up in Marie Joie.
Just a bunch of stuck-up
celestial dragons.
And they're no gods.
I'm not talking about
the world we know today.
I'm talking about the way things were in
the ancient past, long before Marijoa,
before the Celestial Dragons.
They say there was a land of
gods up there, lost to the ages.
I don't know, Pops.
Whoever told you that was
either crazy or playing a prank.
It sounds like a fairy tale, but
this world is full of strange things.
What's the matter with you?
Can you stop daydreaming?
We're in a fight right now.
Guess I was waiting for you to rescue me.
Stop making jokes.
We need to get out of here.
Izo, do you believe in God?
You sound like Pops when he was drunk.
Yo, wake up, you're rookies!
You boys better check yourselves
before you wreck yourselves.
And by the way, nothing you've
thrown at us has done a damn thing!
Let me remind you what they call us.
The Drought.
Wildfire.
And Plague!
We're the three calamities
that protect Commander Kaido!
We're called the lead performers
because we always take center stage!
Hey, what's up with you?
I don't know how to describe it,
but ever since I took off that stupid
raid suit, my body has felt off.
You better not drag me down.
I didn't say I felt sick, all right?
Just feels kind of weird.
Oh, weird, like your eyebrows?
I said my body, you jackass!
That's one you owe me.
Bridal grabber!
I don't owe you shit!
I heard all of Judge's kids are cyborgs.
What part of you is artificial?
Vinsmoke Judge is as crazy as they come.
Bet he got real creative with you.
So, is that burning
leg of yours a machine?
Hate to break it to you, pal, but
unlike my siblings, I'm 100 % human.
Humans can't light themselves
on fire, you moron.
And I know damn well
you're not a Lunarian.
Watch and learn.
This is all natural.
My passion is hotter than fire, so you
better believe I can bring the heat.
I can cook sea monsters with this leg.
I'll cook a dinosaur, too.
I'm gonna show you cyborg technology
that even Vegapot can't touch!
Hope you enjoy the show!
Hey, pay attention, you big-ass mummy!
What the hell kind of blade is that?
You're not a swordsman
you're a killing machine.
Unlike you I don't need formal
style to cut someone down.
No good point you never called yourself
a swordsman in the first place.
Have it your way who
knows how this will go?
By the end of this fight, I might be
tearing your throat out with my teeth.
I'll do whatever it takes to win.
Is that Enma?
It is indeed, boss.
Although I had my misgivings, when Lady
Hiyori said she would give Enma to him,
there was a reason I couldn't stop her.
That sword he took.
If it truly is Shusui?
You should return it to the land of Wano.
Not a chance.
I told you it's my sword.
Then I'll give you a replacement.
It is a sword.
That was handed down to
me From my late father.
Would that be a fair trade?
As long as you can give
me a replacement, fine.
You know, it's strange because
he's a pirate from a foreign land.
But when I look at him, I can't help
but see the young dime-mule of Ringo.
Shimotuki Ushimaru, fighting with us!
That's true!
Why, even their swordplay is similar!
There's another thing.
Lord Ushimaru descended from the
God of the Blade Shimotsuki Ryuma.
The fact that Zorojuro returned Shusui
to the land of Wano feels like fate.
He's even a one-eyed
Samurai, just like Riyuma.
Looks like this is the end of the road.
You can't see the moon, so your
Sulong form won't save you.
Good night, King of the Day!
I forgive you by lying about
the samurai you're hiding.
You already paid the
price with your country.
This is your last chance
to bring rice home.
Otherwise, your leg is coming off.
I swear that I don't
know anyone named Race.
If he's here, I'll cut my own belly.
You are born.
Now suffer!
We would have laid down our lives
a hundred times to protect Race.
Our honor demanded it.
I would have been too ashamed
to return if I had failed.
Are those your last words?
Cause I'm cutting off your head this time!
We have been preparing for this battle
ever since the day Lord Odin died!
We'll avenge our fallen
lord and save Wano!
For two decades we've
asked ourselves are we
still lord odin samurai
here is the answer?
Enough what no how did
you transform again?
Damn it there's a hole in the ceiling
You'll never defile the name
of Kozuki Odin ever again!
We had to reach the final
battle, no matter the cost.
If an ancient city must fall
for us to win, so be it.
If we must sacrifice our lives
to win, then we are ready.
Our victory will bring
a new dawn to the world.
These enemies just keep
pouring out of the castle!
Stay back.
The battle taking place here
is far beyond men like you.
Screw you, pal.
This is our base.
You can't stop us.
You get out of our way or you die.
What'll it be?
If you boys want to stay
alive, I suggest you leave.
Coroneago.
Hello there, Carrot.
Hello there, Wanda. It's Mr. Catviper.
I appreciate you, Karoo, leaving
a piece of this bastard for me.
Let's end this.
If it weren't for Pedro, Luffy and his
allies never would have made it here.
This raid would have failed before
it even had a chance to start.
Pedro again?
You really, Lickety, loved
that bastard, didn't you?
Thinking back on my old friend, I can't
help but gaze at that beautiful full moon.
I'll give Yugara a show, Pedro.
Have a drink or two and enjoy.
Look to the sky, you slobbering Knight.
The view of tonight's full
moon shall be your last.
I thought you were a fool
for serving the ghost
but on second thought
serving that breath is even.
Ah! Silence!
Use is nothing to laugh at!
I was a scoundrel who grew up to be a
samurai, so our lord can grow as well!
Mono will watch over him, as
he will watch over us someday!
But you will not look to see that!
Shadow-pone-jutsu!
With the strength and dedication of
my ninpo, I shall defeat my enemies!
Whoa, you're kidding!
What the hell?
Is that thing a giant dragon?
Why is he here?
Who invited a dragon?
That must be Kaido. What do we do?
Should we fight?
I'm not so sure.
You can count me out. No way!
You will never make a snack out of me!
If you try, I will swallow you whole!
Please step away!
Straw Hat! Be careful!
You sure you're ready?
Are you, Momo?
Indeed.
The kid?
What happened to him?
So, Kaido, is it here? What?
I used my right pride
jutsu on Lord Momonosuke.
I didn't want to do it, but he begged me.
So I turned him into a
28-year-old at his request.
Your power can really do that?
Why are you crying?
Oh, because...
My lord, you!
You look just like you!
Alright!
Let's go, Momo!
We're taking back Wano!
Are you ready?
Of course!
Ah!
What?
Crock, Krieg.
What's going on?
Why did they collapse?
Did something happen, you guys?
Come on, get up!
Oh, it can't be!
This guy can use Kakarazaki!
Seems you figured it out.
Krieg, that's not good!
This is the fate of all who dare to bask
in my presence before
stealing their hearts.
I did take down two Tobiropo after all.
Why, you might as well call
me Sibling Hunter Usohachi!
The Tobiropo!
Two of them!
You can't defy my strength.
Join me by my side.
I don't know why all the bad guys are
passing out, but it sure is handy.
It's because Big Mom is fighting
on the same floor as us.
Only the strong are able to withstand
the power of her conqueror's Haki.
Franky, do you know
what happened to Luffy?
I don't know anything you don't know.
I think what Momo said earlier
is all that matters, though!
Luffy is still alive!
I can hear his voice now!
And he promised me that he'll come back!
I wonder where Momo is?
Shinobu was with him, but
I can't reach her either.
You know what they say,
no news is good news!
Come on, you are not helping.
When you finish your
job, hustle on down here.
Enemy troops are pouring into the
performance floor all of a sudden.
You sure could use a hand. What?
The performance floor?
Hold your ground, bros.
We can't let a single one of them in.
Zoro and Sanshi are fighting two
of the lead performers in there,
and they can't afford to lose.
Aye, aye, but that doesn't
mean I take orders from you.
We're eight boxes! Don't forget it!
Ow! Fire!
Please stop burning me!
Although it would make
sense to cremate me!
No, I'm not ready for that yet!
I still have best to protect!
It's Ferran Corpse! What happened?
The short of it is we need to
get out of the castle quickly.
Do any of you minks know
how the raid is progressing?
All I've seen out there is chaos.
That reminds me, on the way here, I
ran into Jinbei on the fourth floor.
I'm a ball!
Heribus Brickfield!
I haven't heard any news in a while.
Is your captain still battling
against Kaido on the roof?
He beats me.
I've been too busy fighting to find out.
I see.
We can't get bogged down like this.
We need to find the strong
opponents and focus on them instead.
Jimmy, help! It's me, Brook.
We have a situation here.
There's a fire down here on the
third floor, and it's spreading fast.
If you want to get downstairs,
then you'd better hurry!
A fire?
That doesn't sound good, but wait,
the roof, who's keeping
Kaido busy up there?
Give it up, you're
never gonna become Odin.
Why should I listen to
the man who wants me dead?
That was your doing.
This isn't a family quarrel
and it isn't a game.
If you take the name of Odin,
you must be prepared for war.
Do you understand?
You think I should be
punished for admiring someone?
I love Odin, but you can't
take that away from me!
BALLS, I 'LL PROTECT THE
LAND OF WADO, OUT OF MY WAY!
NOW ALL THEN THE PORTERS OF WADO ARE Tang!
Was she always this violent?
No, but she's been terrorizing
us like this all week!
Keep your cool!
Huh?
She may be Commander Kaido's
daughter, but she's still a kid.
There's no way she can
take us all on at once.
Charge in and stop her!
You think you can stop me?
Just try it!
I'll never lose!
I'm begging you, just come quietly!
Please, princess!
I said no! No!
I'm not a princess!
I am...
RUNNING!
She didn't even touch him, did she?
Are you the one responsible
for all this? Yamato? Shut up!
I'm Odin, not Yamato!
I'm Odin!
Answer my question, Yamato.
Are you the one who did this to my men?
I don't know.
They just collapsed on their own.
Hey!
Get these chains off of me, father!
If you don't feed me, I'm gonna die!
Conqueror's Haki, interesting.
You have potential.
But if you've decided you
want to be Odin, then die.
We're enemies!
Hey, stop!
Why don't you cool your
head in here for a while?
A month ought to do the trick.
Where are you going?
Don't leave me in here! It's dark!
A whole month, Commander?
The Ogre Princess is tough, but
there's no way she can survive that!
Besides, there are samurai from the
land of Wano locked up in there!
They're as dangerous as they come!
I'll grant you the same
mercy as my idiot child.
You have one month to get in line.
If you change your mind, shout
through the air hole in the ceiling.
Tell them you want to join my army.
Then I'll let you out of this place.
How many days has it been
since you ate something?
Here, go ahead.
You can have dinner.
Or one of you can.
Swordsmen should not be
without their swords.
Father!
That's not what I know, you're my dad!
They're angry!
It's not safe!
You can't give them their swords!
They're gonna kill me!
Now, why would they want to kill you?
I thought you said you were Odin.
Although I'm Odin, I'm also the
son of Kaido, who killed Odin.
It would be too easy for those
samurai to take their revenge.
Father only put that food there
so we would fight over it.
He wants us to kill each other.
But there's no point in
me thinking about that.
They're going to kill me first.
Go on.
What?
Help yourself.
Don't worry.
Some of I don't get hungry.
Really?
I mean, are you sure about this?
Because I'll eat it.
I'm really hungry, so I'll eat the
whole thing if you don't want it.
Can I?
Of course you can.
Your father's sins are not your own.
I am grateful.
Your jam and I are so tough.
I can't believe you don't get hungry.
Hey, can I become a samurai,
even though I get hungry?
Hands in the air.
Yes, sir!
Calm yourself.
You said that you're Kozuki Odin, right?
We overheard your talk, and I understand.
We love Odin as much as you do.
What name does a fallen Samurai need?
Just call me so-and-so.
I found too many hard words you
had Odin's travel log all this time,
but how?
This world has four seas as well
as one long and narrow waterway.
Apparently he says the planet's
round just like a dumpling.
What a mysterious thing.
How long has it been?
10 days.
I already lost count.
It's all starting to blur together.
Kaido is too cruel.
I can't believe he would let
his own child die like this.
At this rate,
I fear we may not live long enough to
see the battle that Odin predicted.
It'll happen, and when it does,
I'll fight on the side
of Wano and its people.
I'll go out to see like Odin.
I'll become stronger and stronger.
In that case, I won't worry.
Our path is clear.
Dead or alive, there's an important
role for us to play in that war.
To ensure that you won't die here.
20 years is a long time.
Too long for us to wait. I'm afraid.
Wives, you can't do that!
My father is going to kill you for sure!
I'm not going to stay here and
spend my final days rotting away.
We never intended to give in to Kaido
This is the end.
We'll leave the land of Wano to you!
I'm not afraid of you, because
there are people who believe in me,
who accept me for who I am!
Why do you want to take away the
freedom of one of those people?
To take away my freedom?
Life is more than just a series of
questions and answers, you ignorant brats!
WONDERPOWER!